# Stefan Johnson

(C) 775-313-4404 | stefanjohnson650@gmail.com | Renton, WA 98058

#### **SUMMARY**

Focused Fleet service agent skilled in adhering to airfield safety protocols and airline policies. Ready to fulfill challenging new role and apply 8 years of related experience. Accustomed to providing dedicated crew leadership and delegating tasks. I am now also studying to become a web developer because its something I've always wanted to achieve over the years.

### **SKILLS**

- Airline policy implementation
- Crew leadership
- Schedule management

- Airfield safety
- Team management
- MS Office

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Fleet Service Agent, American Airlines, June 2019-Current Seattle, WA

- Adhered to airline cargo policies, monitored operations and reported discrepancies to management for review.
- Maintained safe takeoffs, landings and aircraft operations by directing accurate cargo loading, including placement in relation to aircraft capacity.
- Maximized space in aircraft compartments and staging areas with proper organization and attention to cargo types.
- Delivered packages to customer locations.

## Lead Agent, Envoy Air, January 2018-June 2019 Fort Smith, AR

- Implemented company processes to effectively resolve customer service issues.
- Trained new team members on proper service methods and evaluated service delivery using quality assurance program.
- Worked with senior leadership to address and resolve disciplinary issues and boost overall team success.
- Coached, monitored and motivated new agents to boost performance and enhance job knowledge.
- Handled cash and credit card payments and returned receipts, change and payment cards to customers.
- Escalated issues to correct individuals when typical procedures did not achieve resolution.
- Reviewed backordered products on daily basis, checking item availability and efficiently clearing shipping queues.

• Volunteered to handle complaints and issues for manager during busy time periods.

Cabin Service Supervisor, Delta Global Staffing, August 2015-December 2017 Las Vegas, NV

- Recruited and hired new employees based on company needs and culture.
- Trained employees in proper operational procedures and shared company policies and regulations.
- Observed employee performance and provided valuable feedback using online performance evaluation software.
- Inspected equipment and work stations to comply with established standards and regulations.

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

Some College (No Degree) UFAS, Fort Smith, AR

• Completed coursework in Math, English and Psychology

High School Diploma North Side High School, Fort Smith AR May 2010